When peace, like a
river Attendeth my way
When sorrows
Like sea billows roll
Whatever my lot
Thou hast taught
me to say It is well
It is well with my soul
It is well
With my soul It is well
It is well with my soul
Oh, Lord, haste the day
When my faith shall be sight
The clouds be
rolled back As a scroll
The trump shall resound
And the Lord shall descend
Even so, it is well with my soul
It is well
With my soul It
is well, it is well
With my soul With my soul Whew.
Good. Not bad. Not bad.
And Jerri's pretty
good. What say?
- Yeah.
- Jerri.
Okay, let's stop and
I'll see you on Tuesday.
- Okay.
- Tuesday.
- That was wonderful.
- Oh, thanks.
This choir really means
a great deal to me.
- You've added a lot to it.
- Well, thank you.
Ben didn't say what
a fine singer you are.
Ha, ha. Thanks.
- You're staring.
- I am?
You haven't taken your eyes
off Claire the whole rehearsal.
It's not nice to
stare at a deacon.
I'm so glad you
talked me into this.
I like singing in the choir.
Although singing a solo
scares me half to death.
Well, being a little afraid
makes you sing better.
- I suppose so.
- Yeah.
What's his name again?
- Oh, Jimmy Nash.
- Yeah.
Is he married?
- As far as I know, he lives on his own.
- Yeah.
Seems like a nice guy.
He's a guy, all right.
I'm not sure about the
nice part all the time.
Where are your eyes, ref? Come on,
he just got the hell fouled out of him.
- Come on, ref.
- What's your problem, ref?
He's all over me.
Get in the game, ref.
Come on, ref! Come on!
Forget the bozo, Sipes.
Come on, run the plays.
You would've run the plays,
you wouldn't have been fouled.
Are you sure that's
the same Jimmy Nash?
No, now it's Jimmy Nash, coach.
Different animal. Hey, Jimmy!
Will you call the foul?
Is that a whistle in your
mouth or your thumb?
"Animal" being the key word.
Pass the ball. Pass the ball.
Defense, move it!
Come on, guys!
- What are you looking at?
- Claire.
All right! Yeah!
- She's in the choir.
- Yeah.
Alto.
Yeah. I've always
had a thing for altos.
- Good job!
- Hustle the ball!
Hey, hey, all right!
She looks nice, doesn't she?
Groans nice too.
- Defense.
- Come on.
Sixty-seven to 64, two minutes.
What do you think?
I think she's a beauty.
Pass it!
Set it up. Set it up. Barry.
Sipes. The play, Sipes.
Just pass the ball!
No, the play!
Referee, come on, damn it.
What the hell's the
matter with you?
That ape's been checking him
all night and you haven't called it.
- Sit down, coach.
- You see this? This is a foul.
Call it. You put this whistle
in your mouth and you blow it.
I'm warning you, coach.
What, you're too dumb, too
blind? Why aren't you calling?
Are you in somebody's pocket?
That why you haven't made a call?
- You're out of here.
- Oh, finally, I get a word from you!
You know what you
ought to do, coach?
You ought to sign up for one of
those anger-management courses.
I sold a car to a guy who
gives them last month.
I could probably get you a deal.
Just go outside and watch
the rest of the game, okay, Red?
No, it's too painful.
We're gonna lose.
That was plain as day long before
that little temper tantrum of yours.
That's because that ref
made it a five-on-six game.
No.
We need some new
blood, and that's a fact.
I understand there's a kid in Maryland
that can just shoot the lights out.
Daniel Downing, I
think his name is.
Every school this side of the
Mississippi is looking at that kid.
We don't have a shot at him.
Well, now, what kind of
self-defeating attitude is that?
We got as good a shot
at it as anybody else.
It's just a matter of offering
him the right incentives, that's all.
I've never paid for a player in my
life, and I'm not about to start now.
Money? No.
Working with you,
Jimmy, that's the incentive.
The kid starts his freshman
year, he's a star right off.
He gets the immediate
attention of all the pro scouts,
not to mention a fine
college education, of course.
That's the incentive
I'm talking about.
Recruiting is my job.
Yeah, but you see, as president
of the Baxter Booster Club,
I worry about that too, Jimbo.
I mean, we gotta work together.
You get Daniel Downing down here
and just be your sweet, charming self.
That's all I ask.
Just because this year is a bust,
doesn't mean next year has to be.
- Oh, man.
- Man.
You wanna play on my
team, you stick with the plays.
Shot in the fourth quarter?
The play was busted.
Not from where I was sitting.
Well, maybe you ought to
try it out on the court, coach.
Don't you ever talk to me
like that again. You got that?
Just relax.
All right, come on,
kid, use your body.
You're playing
college kids next year.
All right, give me
something from outside.
Kid's pretty good.
Well, that or the old
man is starting to lose it.
- Hard to tell which.
- Ha, ha.
- Hi, Ron.
- Mr. Tolman.
- All right, that's enough.
- I was hoping you'd say that.
- I'm impressed.
- So am I.
I told you he was
something, didn't I, coach?
Let's go talk in my office.
Good idea.
Well, I've looked
at a lot of programs,
and a lot of programs
have looked at me.
Well, Danny, this is one program
that would love to have you.
If you're looking
for a good education
and a chance to play
some quality basketball,
this is the place to be.
It's starting to look
like that to me too.
You think you might
wanna go with us?
- I know I do.
- Whoa, coach.
I mean, that boy is not
only talented, he's smart.
So when do we discuss the
details of our arrangement?
Danny, why don't you
go on back to the motel...?
What arrangement?
The 30 grand in
cash and the new car.
A sports car, right?
You promised him that?
Jimmy, there's certain things
that you just gotta be realistic about.
Listen, son, no matter
what he's promised you,
we don't pay for players here.
If that's what you're after,
you can get out of here.
- But I...
- Look, look, this is not a payoff.
This is an investment
in this university's future.
And you too, get out!
All right, Jimmy. All
right, all right, take it easy.
Don't tell me to take it
easy! Get out of here!
They're back, man.
Here he comes.
This is my program and I'll run
it the way I want! You got that?
I don't wanna see either
one of you around here again!
What happened?
Yup.
"Death occurred between
9 and 11," it says here.
I was home all night by myself.
Did anybody see
you or talk to you?
I just told you, I
was by myself.
Jimmy, why are you
so calm and nice at choir
and so hostile other
places, especially basketball?
Because nobody
messes with me in choir.
Well, we gotta get this stuff straight,
so you might as well just calm down.
The police found one of
your whistles in his hand,
and the police are saying
that he ripped it off your
neck during a violent struggle.
I've got whistles
hanging all over my office.
Anybody could've stolen
it and planted it there.
And you had words with
Red in the gym yesterday.
Yes. He went behind my back.
He told this kid that
I was trying to recruit
that he was gonna
give him $30,000
and a brand-new sports car if
he'd come and play at Baxter.
I guess that made you mad.
Yeah, it made me mad.
I could've killed him.
Jimbo, I wouldn't
be saying that.
I didn't kill him, Ben.
I swear to you,
I did not kill him.
I'm being framed.
Hi, Claire, Cliff.
Claire, Cliff Lewis from choir.
Claire, Cliff, what's happening?
That's really bad.
- Cliff.
- What?
- What are you doing?
- Nothing.
What's to eat around
here? I'm starved.
Ah, he's got ham and
cheese. You want a sandwich?
Well, if you must know, I was
just thinking about calling Claire
and I was rehearsing
what I was gonna say.
You're gonna ask her out?
Well, I thought about it, but I
don't know if it's such a good idea.
Why, you nervous?
Yeah. But that's
not the problem.
You're afraid she'll say no?
Yeah, probably, but
that's not the problem.
Cliff, what's the problem?
Well, I don't know if she's married.
I don't know anything about her.
Well, why don't you ask her?
Me? Oh, no, no, no, I couldn't
do that. I couldn't do that. No.
- You want me to?
- No. No.
Yes. Yeah.
Yeah, all I wanna do, I wanna
maybe take her for a drive
or to a movie or out to dinner.
Out to lunch. Heh.
Let me ask you a question.
Why don't you have
a man in your life?
I told you, I just broke
up with somebody.
I figured you just told me
that so I wouldn't ask you out.
You didn't believe me?
No.
- Well, you were right.
- Ah.
The truth is
I'm staying not
interested in anyone
- because I've got really bad taste.
- Hmm.
I've spent most of my
life attracted to guys
with great faces,
incredible bodies,
but six months later,
I wake up and I think:
"What am I doing?"
I just can't seem to
pick the right kind of guy.
So I've decided that I'm not
gonna get involved with anybody.
Unless I know the man really well.
He's gonna have to be my best friend.
Yup.
And then we'll see
what happens after that.
Mm, mm. You're right. You're
right, you're right, you're right.
I have to get to know Claire.
That's what I'd do.
But you're gonna
check into her first.
Sure. No problem.
- All right.
- You can count on me.
Great, great,
great. That's great.
I'll do something
nice for you sometime.
Go not far from me
Far from me, O God
Cast me not away
In the time of age
Forsake me not
Forsake me not Forsake me not
When my strength Fail Me
Wonderful, wonderful.
If we get any better, we're
gonna have to get a bigger church.
Let's go ahead and take five.
- Okay.
- Five minutes.
Excuse me.
She smiled at me.
Guess you haven't had a
chance to talk to her yet.
She's recently divorced, no kids,
she works for the gas company,
does a lot of volunteer
work for the church.
She likes to bird-watch
and water-ski.
It's too bad you haven't had
a chance to find anything out.
And she likes to run.
No, run? You're
kidding. Oh, that's great.
Oh, can you find
out when and where?
Parkwood High School, 5:30 p.m.,
Mondays, Wednesdays and Fridays.
Honestly, Cliff, I am so far ahead
of you, you can't even see me.
- See you next week.
- Okay, see you.
Well, the board of trustees
called me this morning.
Said I can't coach
until after the trial.
Unless and until I'm
acquitted. That's how they put it.
The board, huh? Hmm.
Oh, great, a cop.
Now, what does he want?
- Hmm.
- Hello again, coach.
So it's true, you really
do sing in the choir.
What do you want?
Red Tolman's house
was burglarized last night.
Wife heard noises.
Called 911 around 10:15.
So what?
Coach Nash was with me
from, oh, 7:30 till about
11 working on his defense.
He didn't burglarize the house.
- Well, that takes care of that.
- Mm-hm.
You sing in the choir too, Ben?
Oh, yeah, every Sunday.
You ought to come sometime.
I'll keep it in mind.
Oh, yeah, going to church is
a good habit to start and keep.
Makes you feel good.
Calms jittery nerves.
Look at Jimmy.
Joe, if you could find
that out, I'd appreciate it.
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
Red and I met at Baxter.
At a pep rally for a basketball
game against Leland University.
Did he keep his business
files here or at the dealership?
At the dealership.
So most of the stuff that
was stolen out of this cabinet
was probably of
a personal nature?
I suppose so, yes.
Do you have any idea
what these numbers are?
No.
I'll take it in the other room.
Okay.
- Hey, Floyd.
- Yeah. Miss Stone, what's up?
- You done working in here?
- Yep.
In about five minutes, we'll
be done working out here.
What you got?
A nice clear
podiatric calling card.
A footprint, huh?
A big footprint.
Cool.
Keep moving. Get the open shot.
That's it. That's it.
All right.
No, Barry.
You made your cut too soon.
Let the play develop.
You're not supposed
to be coaching, Jimmy.
I mean, if this kid
would just concentrate.
Hmm. I'll tell you what,
let's talk in your office.
- What are you doing?
- Come on, come on. Come on. Ah.
Pike, that is your shot.
Take it when it's there.
Come on. Come on.
Send it back out.
- Oh.
- Go on to your office.
I'll meet you there.
Go on. Go on.
Now, I hear the police found
a footprint made by your shoe
- outside Red's house.
- Yeah.
They think you broke
in there last night.
I used to go to parties
there all the time,
so even if that was my
footprint, I didn't break in.
You always enter the house
through the window, Sipes?
You broke in because there
was proof Red was paying you.
That's a lie. That's a lie.
- Jimmy...
- How much did you make?
Hey, at least I didn't kill anybody!
You'll never coach again! You'll never...
And you'll never play again!
I want you, coach. Come on,
let's go. Right now. Right now.
- I top you, my friend.
- Right now!
- Let's get out of here.
- Right now. Come on.
Claire. Hey. Cliff,
from the choir.
- Yeah. Sure. How you doing?
- Oh, great, great. How you doing?
- Good.
- Good. That's great.
- You come running here a lot?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- All the time.
- Really?
- Same 16 laps, year in, year out. Heh.
Oh. Well, why don't, uh...? Why
don't we go running sometime?
You know, I could
show you some routes
and broaden your
horizons a little.
- Yeah. That'd be great.
- Great.
Well, that's it for me. I'll
see you at choir practice?
- Yeah, great. Great.
- Okay.
Nice running into you. Bye-bye.
See you next time.
I used to think that
losing your temper like that
was something
you did just for show,
but you got a real
problem, you know that?
Yeah, yeah, I know.
You lose it like that in
front of a judge and jury...
Okay, okay, I get the picture.
You'd better get the picture.
So you think this
boy, Ron Sipes...?
You think Red was paying him
on the sly to come here and play?
God knows how many other
kids he tried to recruit like that.
I'm sure God knows a lot
more than we think he does.
Well, we'll get some subpoenas
and have a look at a few bank records,
see what we come out with.
Oh, this was found
on Red's desk.
Mean anything to you?
No.
Oh. Hi, Barry. Come on in.
Ben, this is Barry Glover.
- Oh, Ben Matlock.
- Hi.
That slam dunk of yours
just takes my breath away.
Ha, ha. Thanks. Ahem.
Uh, I need to talk to you.
About?
The, uh, Red Tolman thing.
Well, Mr. Matlock is my attorney,
son. You can talk in front of him.
The police came by
my place this morning
and asked me a
bunch of questions.
What did they want with you?
Well, see, the night of the
murder, I went over to your house.
You told me if I ever had trouble in
any of my classes to make sure I got help,
and Ancient World History has
been giving me fits this semester.
Anyway, uh, I rang
the bell at the front door,
went around to the side,
but you weren't there.
I guess one of your neighbors
saw me and recognized me.
What time was that?
Around 9:30.
I couldn't lie. I mean, your
car was gone and everything.
Don't worry about it.
I'm sorry, coach.
It's okay.
You did the right thing.
You just work on that jumper.
Where were you?
I can't tell you.
You lied to me and
you lied to the police.
- Ben...
- I'm working my butt off for you.
Look, temper, Ben. People
lie to their lawyers all the time.
Not to this lawyer, they
don't. I want the truth.
I didn't kill Red Tolman.
I'm sorry about the lie,
but I didn't kill the man.
I understand you play basketball for
the Baxter Cougars. Is that correct?
I used to.
I've been declared
ineligible by the NCAA.
And why's that?
I took money from Red Tolman.
The decedent was paying you
to play basketball for Baxter?
Yeah.
See, he gave me a
job at his car dealership,
only I didn't have to show up.
I just collected a paycheck.
Did anyone else know
about this arrangement?
Yes, ma'am.
The man who turned
me in, Coach Nash.
- That's a lie. That's a lie.
- Order.
That's a damn lie, and
he damn well knows it!
- Time out.
- Order.
- He's lying!
- Time out.
Order.
Mr. Matlock.
Five minutes.
You wanna get mad?
Here, get mad.
Jump up and down on it.
Throw it against the wall.
Throw it out the window.
Do any asinine thing you want
to to get it out of your system.
- Ben, look...
- You know how I told the lieutenant
that going to church calms
jittery nerves? Not you.
The old hymn we like to sing:
"In that far off sweet forever,
just beyond the shining river,
when they ring the golden
bells for you and me."
You keep yelling and cussing
in the courtroom like that,
they ain't gonna ring
no golden bells for you.
You just testified that
Coach Nash knew all along
that Red Tolman was
paying you under the table,
and that Coach Nash turned
you in to the NCAA. Is that right?
- Yes, it is.
- Then I just have one other question.
If Coach Nash knew all
along about those payments,
why would he turn you in knowing that
you'd just turn around and turn him in?
Objection.
Calls for speculation.
Yeah, I guess it
does. Nothing further.
The morning sun Dispels
the darkened cloud
Sun of my soul, I cry aloud
To thee for faith and
strength To carry on
Through darkest
night Till break of dawn
The morning sun
Gives birth to every day
To thee, my God I kneel and pray
Better and better.
We keep singing like
this, we get to heaven,
we're gonna have a job.
- Okay. See you next time.
- Okay.
- Bye.
Claire.
- Hi. Ready to go for that run?
- Hey. Hi.
- Um, yeah. Sure.
- Great.
Why don't you meet me at
my house so I can change,
- and we'll go from there?
- Great. Excellent.
- Okay. Do you know where it is?
- Yeah.
- Okay. Bye.
- Sounds good. All right.
That was a good run, Cliff.
I didn't even know
the park was there.
Yeah, I discovered it when I
was training for the triathlon.
You were in a triathlon?
Yeah, a small one. It
was up in Wilmington.
I didn't win or
anything, but I did finish.
Well, that's great. That's
better than I could've done.
I don't know. You seem
like you're in good shape.
Thanks.
Uh, well, I would invite you in
for some water or something,
but I'm kind of
pressed for time.
- Oh. We'll try it some other time, then.
- Definitely. Definitely.
So, uh, I'll see you
at choir practice?
Choir practice, right.
- Okay. Bye.
Mm. I'm all sweaty.
- Running, huh?
- Mm-hm.
With Cliff
from the choir and
Ben Matlock's office.
Oh.
Well, he's been asking
and kind of flirting.
I thought it wouldn't hurt.
It's okay, isn't it?
Sure.
Mm. Don't you want
me to take a shower?
Later.
- Hi, Claire.
- Jerri. What are you doing here?
Ben wanted me to find out
why Jimmy lied about his alibi,
so I've been following
him. Can I talk to him?
- Let her in, Claire.
- Well...
So how long has
this been going on?
What are you talking
about? Nothing's going on.
Nothing?
Do all of your friends
have keys to your place?
It's okay, Claire. She knows.
- Were you here the night of murder?
- Yes.
Jimmy, that means
she can give you an alibi.
- You've gotta come forward with this.
- See, she can't give me an alibi.
I was here, but Claire wasn't.
I parked in the fire lane
behind the library that night,
and my car was towed.
I got here about 11:00.
And that's why I lied to Ben.
Claire's just recently been divorced,
and I was seeing her before that.
And the church is
very important to Claire,
so I decided not to make
it more difficult for her.
And because telling the truth wouldn't
have done me any good anyway.
In college basketball,
scandal-rocked Baxter
- takes on Iowa Tech at The Barn.
- Excuse me.
Despite the loss of
outside gunner Ron Sipes
and volatile coach Jimmy Nash,
the Cougars are still ten-point
favorites. In other hoop action...
- Cougars are still gonna win, honey.
- Hold on.
And out west, surging Stanford
is picked to beat USC by four.
Call Ben, tell him to
meet me at my office.
Those numbers are point spreads.
I went through all 26 games
that we played last season
and I wrote down the
point spread for each game,
which is apparently
what Red did.
Why are some of them circled?
Because those are the games
where we didn't cover the point spread.
We either lost by more
than we were expected to
or we won by less than
we were expected to.
And if Red looked at this tape,
he would have discovered
what I discovered.
In every single
one of these games
it was Barry Glover who
made or missed the shot
that determined the final score.
Barry was throwing the games?
He was shaving points.
Probably making
a fortune in bets.
Red loved the Cougars more
than life, and he bought players,
but he never would
have stood for that.
Daggone.
I said "daggone." I
didn't say "damn."
You know, Red told his wife
that he was going out to
do some errands that night.
Hmm.
- Wonder where he went.
- I don't know.
What about his effects?
Find anything unusual?
- No.
- Hmm.
Hmm, hmm, hmm.
- Here's that crazy car of his.
- Oh.
The Cougarmobile.
- He drove that thing everywhere.
- Yeah.
Yeah. I used to see him
around town blowing his horn
and waving like he was some
kind of homecoming queen.
I didn't see it
outside, did you?
- Uh-uh.
- Huh.
Wonder how he
got here that night.
Well, now, that's
a good question.
If he had driven here that night,
he'd have parked his car right here.
Old Red, God rest
his soul, kind of lazy.
Believed in parking as
close to the door as he could.
Yeah.
Whose car is that?
Well, I didn't know.
It's not from our dealership, so
I called the automobile registry
and found out it's registered to
somebody named Daniel Downing.
It was purchased
the very day Red died.
Keys are right here.
It's brand-new, all right. It's
got less than 100 miles on it.
Different dealership.
I bet Red left his
car over there,
drove this car here so
he could deliver it to...
- What was his name?
- Daniel Downing.
Yeah. Later that night.
What are you doing?
Thinking.
Pop this thing here.
It's empty.
What happened there?
Uh, I missed.
The Cougars were
favored to win by six.
You missed two foul
shots. They won by four.
What about this game?
I screwed up again.
And because of it, the
Cougars won by three
instead of the five
they were supposed to.
- What about this game?
- Your Honor.
Mr. Matlock, I take it
this, uh, blooper reel
is somehow relevant
to the case at hand?
- Yes, sir.
- Then tell us how now.
Yes, sir.
Tell me something, Barry.
Why is it that all last season,
most of your screw-ups
came at the last
minutes of the game?
Even great players get
tight at the end of a game.
But not quite as often as you.
You were shaving
points, weren't you?
No.
You weren't being paid to
manipulate the point spread
so that somebody could make
a killing betting on your games?
No, that's a lie.
You were doing it on your own?
If I was shaving points for
myself or somebody else,
either way, I'd be rich.
And I'm not rich. I mean,
ask anyone who knows me.
I live in a dorm. I drive a
beater. I had to borrow this coat.
You're smart.
You got a lot of
money, but you're smart.
You figured this clever way to
hide your point-shaving money.
- Your Honor.
- Mr. Matlock.
I'm about to bring it
home, Your Honor.
Bring it on in.
When's the last time you spoke
to the decedent, Red Tolman?
I don't know.
Well, according to
the telephone records,
he called your private
room in the dormitory
on the 23rd of last month
at 3:09 in the afternoon.
That sound about right?
Yeah, I guess.
Hmm. That was the
day he was murdered.
What did he wanna talk about?
Basketball, I guess. That's all
he ever wanted to talk about.
More specifically, he wanted to
talk about point shaving, didn't he?
- No.
- Oh, come on, now.
You see this piece of paper?
It was found on Red's
desk in his house.
See these numbers?
See these circled numbers?
He figured out that
you were shaving points
and he was gonna
turn you in, wasn't he?
- No.
- I bet he was.
And I bet you begged
to talk to him first,
- in private that night at his office.
- Never happened.
Only you didn't meet him
there, you got there early.
And you didn't talk to him.
You hit him over the
head and killed him.
- That's not true.
- And then you trashed the place
and planted one of Coach
Nash's whistles there
so it would look like he
had done it in a fit of anger.
- I didn't do any of that.
- Yes, you did.
And this proves it.
See that?
There's a basketball
player, Daniel Downing.
Red was gonna pay him
to play for the Cougars.
Thirty thousand dollars
in cash and a car,
a brand-new white sports car.
Coach Nash turned down the deal,
but Red had the
money, he had the car.
I saw it myself parked
in front of his dealership.
The police searched
your room this morning.
They found this briefcase.
It's nice. I mean,
it's high quality.
You can't buy a briefcase like
this but one place in this town.
And Cliff Lewis had the shop
owner go through his records.
And guess what.
This briefcase
wasn't bought by you,
it was bought by Red Tolman.
Now, how could that be?
How about this?
After you killed him
and wrecked the place,
you tried to leave.
But you couldn't.
Somebody had parked
a car behind your car.
See, without thinking, you
had parked in Red's space,
so he just pulled up behind you.
So you went back inside, got
the key, came back outside,
and moved the sports
car one space over.
And you saw the briefcase.
And you opened it and you saw
the $30,000, so you took them.
And you squirreled that 30,000 away
with your other point-shaving money
and hid the briefcase in
the closet of your dorm room,
never imagining that one
day it would incriminate you.
But it doesn't incriminate me.
Red gave that briefcase to
me long before that, as a gift.
No.
The shop owner's records show
that this briefcase was sold to
Red the day he was murdered.
The only way you could
have wound up with it
is if you killed him.
You'd have been better off to
let him turn you in, wouldn't you?
Don't you hear The
bells now ringing?
Don't you hear
the angels singing?
'Tis the glory
hallelujah jubilee
In that far-off sweet forever
Just beyond the shining river
When they ring the golden bells
For you and me You and me
Yeah. Ha, ha.
- Ah.
- That was great, huh?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- That was great, yeah.
Let's go get some peanut butter
and crackers or popcorn or something.
Yeah, yeah. All's well
that ends well. Yeah.
- Jimmy's okay, the choir sounds good.
- Mm.
All's well that ends well.
- Yeah.
- Cliffy, I'm sorry about Claire.
It wasn't meant to be.
- She was pretty, though, wasn't she?
- Yeah.
Is it ever gonna be meant to be?
Well, sure.
There's another old song:
"I'm blue, but I
won't be blue always
because the sun's gonna
shine in my back door someday."
It'll be okay, Cliff. You
ain't over the hill yet.
- You ain't even to it. Ha, ha.
- Yeah.
Let's go toast with some
peanut butter and jelly.
Oh, that sounds good.
www.tvsubtitles.net